In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
Not my choice...
I was not...
I was not born as a woman by choice!
What I can't forgive is how your
selfishness nearly got Griffith killed!
I don't care if you drop dead
somewhere in battle!
But I'll never forgive you if you ruin the
Band of the Hawk, Griffith's dream!
And I can't forgive you for
making Griffith change like he has...
Why?
Why did he choose you?
Why you?
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
Prepared for Death
What's the matter?
Are you giving up?
Oh brother, a woman
can be such a nuisance.
A woman has no strength. She can
lose her temper at the drop of a hat.
Not only that, but you're on your period.
At any rate, women just aren't cut out for war.
You know nothing about women!
Of course not. I'm a man, so how could I know?
What I do know is that
we don't have the time...
...to be stranded here
by your woman problems any longer.
The enemy doesn't care about your
condition or if you are a woman or not.
On second thought...
they are probably glad, wouldn't you say?
Let's move!
What the hell?
Hey, is this a breeding ground
for swarms of mosquitoes?
I found you.
I am glad you are alive, kid!
Hey, old man,
you're looking pretty good yourself.
Shut up!
Even though it was a fluke, a bastard
like you caused me some real trouble.
I, a proud Tudor knight, could not bear
to die without rectifying the situation!
Oh, really?
I'm not going to let you die easily.
I will haul you off as a captive
and expose you to hell on earth.
You'll enjoy a secret torture technique,
the 100-year Monzetsu Goroshi...
...that has been passed down through
the Coborlwitz family for 200 years!
I didn't think you'd still be holding a grudge.
If you surrender without protest, I'll spare you.
But if you want to cross us...
...we'll chop off your arms along
with any other body parts we like!
So long as you're alive, it does not matter.
As for the woman, we will make her
a plaything for my soldiers right here!
I have to suggest that you don't try that.
She is a truly scary woman.
She'll rip you to shreds.
How dare you joke around with me!
Beat them down!
I don't need your help anymore!
Great!
Damn!
There are only two of them!
Don't hesitate!
Overwhelm them in a single charge!
They are incompetents, every one of them.
Samson!
Here, Big Brother!
Assistant commander of the Blue
Whale Heavy Assault Knights...
Samson!
He is my younger brother and second
strongest warrior in my entire unit!
Additionally, Samson's armor is three
times as thick as anyone else's!
Even buried under an avalanche,
he would be absolutely indestructible!
On top of that, his iron ball can crush
a buffalo's head flat in a single blow!
If a man gets hit squarely by it,
nothing will remain but a piece of flesh!
Now, I give you no quarter!
Have them experience firsthand...
...the esteemed techniques
of the Coborlwitz family!
A sword would be smashed
if used to block his attacks directly.
What should we do?
He knocked it back?
I can't believe it...
He's beating back every blow
from Samson's iron ball...
Oh, I see!
He has no time to dodge the blows
because of their incredible speed!
No...
With Guts's skill...
...he should be able to evade and attack.
There's no need for him
to damage his sword like that...
He's protecting me...
He's injured...
The arrow wound I inflicted upon you when...
...you were trying to protect that
woman seems to be bothering you!
Quit your dawdling!
He's been injured!
Finish him off quickly!
Hey!
I'll clear the way for you...
...and then you sprint for the woods.
But...
What the...
S-Samson...
Now!
Get away from here!
Get your ass moving!
Run!
But...
What are you doing?
Go right now!
No way...
I just can't...
I won't leave without you!
Shoot!
Aim for the woman and kill her off!
Foolish!
You repeatedly get wounded
on behalf of a mere woman.
How stupid you are!
Why?
Don't get the wrong idea.
A sickly person is of no use
here, so I want you to get lost.
It's not my nature to evade the enemy.
Besides, I've got to get even
with that sniveling bastard.
As you said, maybe
I'm content just wielding my sword...
But you're different, right?
Do you want to die in a place like this?
Do you want to die a meaningless
death in this little skirmish?
Has the wish you hold in
your heart rotted away that much?
There are times when
a sword needs to be sheathed.
Go back to the sheath that protects you.
Go back to Griffith.
Hurry up!
Run!
Go!
Get out of here!
I promise to return with our comrades!
Don't die until then!
Don't let her get away!
Get her and kill her off!
You shouldn't go chasing after
women until you get your work done...
...you scheming cowards!
You bastard!
W-What a man!
He beats armored men as if
they were cherries to be picked.
It's unbelievable, but a man drops
every time he swings his sword!
I didn't know that such a man
existed among the enemy lines.
My sword is blunt.
The blade has gotten dull.
However, it's three times as thick and
three times as heavy as any other.
Just hope you die when I hit you,
or you'll be in lots of pain.
You son of a bitch!
Look here!
All of you, stop dawdling!
Though he is skilled, the enemy
is only one wounded man!
All we have to do is
surround him, and he'll be finished!
We number one hundred men!
Get him!
Don't talk nonsense.
Is there anyone who wants
to take revenge for Samson?
No one wants to.
Are you all really proud knights of Tudor?
Actually, we're mercenaries over here.
I will pay triple the reward
I promised if someone beheads him...
No, wait. I'll even increase the amount by five...
And I'll guarantee your promotion
to battalion commander!
F-Five times the reward...
What should we do?
Naturally, we've got to give it a shot.
It looks like he can't move around
too much with that wound.
It'll be possible if we get a group
of five men or so to challenge him.
What are you bitching about?
I'm leaving then.
That's right.
That's how mercenaries have to be.
Right?
Pursuers?
Four...
No, there are five...
Die!
Pull yourself together!
Damn it, that bitch...
Get her!
What are you doing?
Kill him at once!
We did it!
Good!
We've crippled his left hand now!
He won't be able to wield
his huge sword so easily.
Beat him!
Now it's getting interesting.
This is the end...
I can't run anymore...
Oopsie, I bet you'd like to get your hands on that.
You put us through a lot of trouble, girl.
We can put you out of
your misery soon, but...
A whole bunch of my comrades
were killed by you, so...
Before killing you off,
I've got to thank you for that.
Don't glower at me like that.
I'm offering you all the fun you want
right before setting out for the afterlife.
You should show me some gratitude.
Well, well...
What's wrong?
Are you embarrassed?
I don't care if you command
a thousand men in battle or not...
Now look at you. You don't seem
to have any authority over me at all.
I'm unable to push this bastard aside...
Why...
Why is my arm so powerless...
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...